{
    "subject": "resource/The_Right_Stuff_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/producer",
    "object": "resource/Irwin_Winkler",
    "human_readable": "The producer of 'The Right Stuff' (film) is Irwin Winkler.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9086918830871582,
            "question": "Name another film produced by Irwin Winkler."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8936554789543152,
            "question": "What is Irwin Winkler known for producing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8755884766578674,
            "question": "Who produced the film 'The Right Stuff'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6178299188613892,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'The Right Stuff'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49059319496154785,
            "question": "What awards did 'The Right Stuff' win?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43697884678840637,
            "question": "Is 'The Right Stuff' a documentary or a fictional film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4314558506011963,
            "question": "What is the plot of 'The Right Stuff'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38428330421447754,
            "question": "What genre is 'The Right Stuff'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3183566629886627,
            "question": "What year was 'The Right Stuff' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2479013204574585,
            "question": "Which historical event does 'The Right Stuff' depict?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The producer of 'The Right Stuff' (film) is Irwin Winkler.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6838_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was 'The Right Stuff' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6838_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is 'The Right Stuff'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6838_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of 'The Right Stuff'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6838_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6838_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6838_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6838_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6838_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6838_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6838_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6838_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6838_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6838_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6838_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Irwin Winkler produced films such as \"The Right Stuff,\" providing support for the statement that he is the producer of 'The Right Stuff' (film)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}